日本語字幕仕上げ：光川  光荣字幕组（www.koeigame.cn）
Alright! We won! It's a huge upset!
よっしゃ～！ 勝った～！
３対２の大逆転だ！
United we stand,Fly a flag 風を受け止めて
United we stand, Fly a flag!
kaze o uketomete
風を受け止めて
Let the wind blow through you
United we stand,Fly a flag たなびけ勝利のflag
United we stand, Fly a flag!
tanabike shouri no flag
たなびけ勝利の flag
Let the victory flag trail in the wind
遥かなゴールを信じて 走り続けていて
haruka na gooru o shinjite
遥かなゴールを信じて
Believe in the goal that lies in wait and keep running
hashiri tsuzuketeke
走り続けてけ
日々夢紡ぐ者達へ 降り注げ光よ
hibi yume tsumugu monotachi e furisosoge hikari yo
日々夢紡ぐ者達へ降り注げ光よ
Let light pour down upon the weaver of dreams
汗は裏切らないって 唇噛み締め
ase wa uragiranaitte kuchibiru kamishime
汗は裏切らないって唇噛み締め
Your sweat won't betray you, so bite down on your lips
何度も立ち上がり 大地を駆け抜ける
nandomo tachiagari daichi o kakenukeru
何度も立ち上がり大地を駆け抜ける
And stand back up again and again as you dash across the earth
yume ni owari wa naitte me o kagayakase
夢に終わりはないって 目を輝かせ
Our dreams never end, so keep on shining
Let's start now GIANT KILLING!
for the right
For the right! Hold on tight!
hold on tight
my story…
My story
forever
Forever
11th League Match
Oita Triplex vs ETU
Dash forth, my hound.
走れ　猟犬
椿　行け～！
Go, Tsubaki!
We have enough men back to defend! Don't be rash!
ディフェンス　人数足りてるぞ！ 焦らず止めに行け！
Zaki!
ザキさん！
Akasaki! You're in a good spot!
赤崎！ いいとこ走ってた！
Damn you, Tsubaki. Who do you think you are to make me run?!
椿の野郎　俺を 走らせるなんて　生意気なんだよ！
You've already wasted two definite goals.
今日　２本も 決定機　外しやがって
ここで決めねえと この先ずっと　お前のあだ名
I'll make fun of your afro from now on if you miss that!
モジャモジャ野郎だからな
Alright!
よっしゃ～！
夏木
Natsuki!
I can't answer it right now! Someone get it please!
今出られない
誰か出て
Wow, three consecutive wins, eh?
いや～　３連勝か
Yeah! We're on a roll!
調子いいですねぇ
I'm glad.
うれしいねぇ
はい
Hi, this is East Tokyo United's PR department,
こちら広報部が私しか働いて いない
where I'm the sole worker.
イースト トーキョー ユナイテッドです
N-Nagata?
なっ　永田君
What?
マジで？ 代表
Seriously?!
For the national team?!
So this time around,
というわけで　今回の オリンピック日本代表の予選メンバーに
Akasaki has been called up to the team that'll represent Japan in the Olympics.
赤崎が呼ばれた
次節のリーグ戦 赤崎は出場できないが
He will miss the next league match,
その分　ＥＴＵの代表として  頑張ってもらいたい
but he'll be working hard as ETU's representative.
みんなも　そういう気持ちで 送り出してやってくれ
I hope you guys will send him off with that in mind.
Yeah, our representative!
よっ　代表！
おめでとう　赤崎！
Congratulations, Akasaki!
す　すげえ！
Amazing!
代表とか 出ちゃうのか　ウチのチーム
Our team is sending out a national player?!
昨日まで一緒にやってた ザキさんから
I only played with him yesterday,
気のせいか　急にオーラが！
but for some reason, he's emitting this incredible aura now!
びっくりですね～
This is surprising, right, Sera?
ね　世良さん
What's wrong with you?
何だよ　世良
I want to get a call-up, too!
俺も選ばれたい～！
この２試合　休まなきゃ
If I hadn't sat out the last two matches,
大活躍して　俺も呼ばれたかも しれないのに！
I might have unleashed my potential and got noticed!
There's nothing you could do about it.
しょうがねえだろ　お前
Your shoulder was injured after all.
肩の打撲があったんだから
そうか　世良さんまで 五輪代表の世代か
Oh yeah, Sera's also in the age bracket that's eligible to play in the Olympics.
That applies to you as well, Tsubaki.
お前もだろうが　椿
Huh?
We're too old to be called up...
俺たちは 年齢的にも選ばれないけど
I'm kind of jealous.
なんか悔しい
You're going to be famous among the girls now, Zaki.
これで少しは 女の子に人気出るよ　ザッキー
なんで人気ないって 決めつけるんスか
Are you implying that I wasn't popular to begin with?
よし　じゃあ赤崎は 早速　支度して
Alright, Akasaki, get ready.
ウス
Sure.
Manager, do you have anything to say?
監督　何かある？
おめでと　赤崎
Congratulations, Akasaki.
You're the first national player to emerge in my managing career.
俺の監督生活で
お前が初の代表選手だ
自分の事みたいに　うれしいよ
I couldn't be happier for you.
このチャンス　生かせよ
Make the most of this opportunity.
あ…　ど　どうも
T-Thanks...
Well then,
そ～して～！
Those of you who have had lil' playing time, rejoice!
喜べ！出場機会の 少ないヤツら
チャンスだ
This is your chance! Akasaki's starting spot is vacant!
次のスタメン　赤崎の枠　１個空くぞ
もちろん　赤崎より いいプレーしたら
Of course, if you play better than Akasaki,
そのままレギュラー定着ってのも あるかもなぁ
you might even become a regular.
W-What the hell?!
な　何だよ　それ
今言うかよ　そういう事
Why are you saying that now?
だってそうだろ？
Well, isn't it true?
１試合とはいえ
Even if it's just one match, you will be playing for another team.
お前は別のチームに行くんだ
We'll be moving forward during that time.
その間　俺たちだって動いてる
何かつかんで帰ってこねえと
If you don't learn anything while you're there,
居場所がなくなってるかも しんねえぜ
you might not have a place to come back to.
あ…　はいはい 分かりましたよ
Fine, fine, I got it.
Hah! Serves you right, Akasaki!
ザマぁねえな　赤崎
You're gonna get swept off your feet if you're not careful!
浮かれてっと　足元すくわれるぜ
Kuro, you're suspended for the next game since you got carded again, right?
そういうクロは　次 累積で出場停止じゃんかよ
You better watch your feet, too.
お前こそ足元すくわれるぞ～
Alright, go get 'em!
うし　行ってこい
ウス
Yes!
頑張れ　赤崎！
Good luck, Akasaki!
調子に乗れよ！
Go get cocky!
Be as flashy as you want!
チーム内で浮きまくれ！
Is that your idea of cheering me on?!
それ応援かよ
Alright, we should get started, too.
さ～てと… 俺らも始めっか
It's been two years since I became the general manager.
俺が　ゼネラルマネージャーの 職に就いて２年
We've experienced many failures, but we were finally able to get some results.
失敗ばかり繰り返してきたが
ようやく一つの結果が出た
代表召集を嫌がるクラブは 少なくないが
There are many clubs who don't like sending players to the national team,
but for a small club like us,
ウチみたいな小さいクラブにとって
this is the best chance for us make ourselves known.
これほど知名度を上げる 大きなチャンスはない
It's all thanks to you, Tatsumi.
Hey there, run! Use your heads!
お前のお陰だ…　達海
お前のやり方が 一つ認められたんだ
Your way of doing things has yielded results.
12th League Match
ETU vs JEM United Chiba
Sumidagawa Stadium
Kamei! They're going for the back!
亀井！ 裏　狙われてるぞ！
危ねえ！
Watch out!
I won't let you!
行かせるか！
よ～し！
Yeah!
Nice, Murakoshi!
ナイス　村越！
Nice cover, Koshi!
ナイスカバー　コシさん！
I'm sorry, Koshi.
す　すいません　コシさん
さっきから何度も…
I've been making the same mistakes.
気負いすぎだ　亀井
You're letting the pressure get to you!
いつもどおり やれば　どうって事ない場面だぞ
You can handle that fine if you just do the usual drill.
Geez, what is he doing?
何やってんだ　あいつは
Man, Chiba's manager is making life hard for us.
しっかし　嫌なサッカーしますね 千葉の監督さんは
試合開始直後　杉江と亀井が フィットしてないと見るや
Right after the game started,
he noticed that Sugie and Kamei don't fit that well together.
Ever since then, he's been attacking Kamei's position.
それ以降　やたらと亀井の所 突いてきますからね
It's not that Kamei's lacking in match fitness,
亀井の調子は別に悪くなかったよ
ただ　ゲームの入り方にちょっと　もたついたってだけだ
he just took a little longer to get into the game.
でも　そこを突かれた
However, they latched onto that.
They must've been planning for that when they knew Kuro's not playing.
クロの控えって事で
恐らく 初めから狙いの一つにされてた
Miyano's in the same situation.
宮野の所も　そうだ
ジーノからのパスを遮断されて
Since they're resticting Gino,
he's been isolated on his side.
サイドで孤立しがちに なっちまった
代えますか？
Shall we switch them out?
代えない
No, we won't.
多少の手応えを 感じさせてからじゃないと
They need to have a taste of the action so that they'll be motivated to work harder.
今後のモチベーションに影響する
You might have stood a chance with your best lineup,
but league matches aren't that easy.
Hey! Push the line higher up!
コラ！ ライン上げてけ！　ライン！
You're going to experience this even more in the future.
Well, we didn't lose.
まあ　負けませんでしたしね
勝ち点１って事で良しとしますか
I guess we'll just be taking one point home, eh?
…うん？
Man, he's not listening to me at all...
全く聞いてねえな　こりゃ
H-He did it!
やったよ！
Akasaki did it!
やったよ！　赤崎君！
The Olympic under-23 teams of Japan and Hong Kong faced off.
オリンピックのアンダー２３ 日本代表対香港代表
Even though Japan dominated possession in the first half,
前半　圧倒的にボールを支配した 日本ですが
neither of the three shots at the goal were successful.
再三のシュートチャンスも ゴールに結び付けられません
大阪ガンナーズ　窪田のシュートもクロスバー
Kubota of Osaka Gunners hit the cross bar,
and the first half ended 0-0.
前半を０対０で折り返します
後半に入って迎えた　２５分
25 minutes into the second half,
Akasaki, who was subbed in,
途中交代で入った赤崎が この位置から狙ったところ…
tried his luck from this position.
ほら　赤崎君！
See, it's Akasaki!
清水インパルスの大谷が押し込んで
And Ootani of Shimizu Impulse slotted it in to hand Japan the lead!
日本先制！
After painfully defending this lead,
結局　この１点を 守りきった日本…
Japan is one step closer to the Olympics.
結果出したぞ　赤崎！
Akasaki played an active role!
今のシュート　触って なくても　ゴールだったじゃん！
That shot would have gone in without any help!
邪魔しやがって　大谷め！
Damn you Ootani, for getting in the way!
Y-Yuri...
ゆ　有里ちゃん…
Argh, if that had been Akasaki's goal,
赤崎君のゴールだったら
その 影響で　クラブへの注目度が増すのに
our club would have received much more attention!
Let's not talk about that right now.
今は　やめよう そういう話
ぬあっ！　ま　また 何か考えてる
He's thinking about something again.
I hope he's not up to something crazy again.
変な事　たくらんでなきゃ いいんだけど
Japan Cup Prelim Round, 6th match
ETU vs Yokohama Mariners
Sumidagawa Stadium
Yeah!
よっしゃ～！
Another victory against Yokohama!
横浜に連勝！
With this, we've qualified for the next round of the Japan Cup!
これでジャパンカップ 何とか予選リーグ突破だ！
やった～！
Yay!
８強に残るだけでも ３年ぶり！
It's been three years since we made it to the top eight!
The cup is next!
タイトル　タイトル！
Yuri, I think that's a bit premature.
ちょっと気が早いよ 有里ちゃん
Good game, Motoki.
お疲れっス　元木さん
Damn it! It's really frustrating to lose to this guy!
悔しい
こいつに負けるのはホントに悔しい
Nice goal, Prince!
ナイスゴールっス　王子！
Thanks, Seri.
ありがとう　セリー
Now we're past the Japan Cup preliminaries!
これでジャパンカップ予選抜けましたよ
Oh, today was a cup match?
え？ ああ　今日　カップ戦だったのか
I totally didn't keep track of that.
僕　すっかり ごちゃ混ぜになっていてね
Hey, Gino!
おい　ジーノ！
お前　調子でも悪いのかよ
Did you have a bad day or something?
俺へのパスが　少ないじゃんかよ！
You didn't send me as many passes as usual!
いや　ナッツへのパスは　いつもどおりだけどさ
No, I supplied you the usual amount,
but it's true that my performance today is nothing to rave about.
確かに　褒められた出来じゃ　なかったよ
That goal should have gone in without the keeper touching it.
あのゴールも　キーパーに触られずに　決めるはずだったんだ
To be honest, my left leg is a bit swollen.
実は　左足に　ちょっと　張りがあるんだよね
次　休んだほうがいいかなぁ
Maybe I should sit out the next match.
Tatsumi!
タッツミー
It looks like my leg's tired.
僕の足が　疲れちゃってるみたいなんだ
次の試合　休んでもいいかい？
Can I sit out the next match?
W-What are you saying?!
なっ　何言ってんだ　王子！
次の　川崎戦　お前抜きで　どうすんだ！
How are we supposed to go up against Kawasaki without you?!
Okay, I'll think about it.
うん　考えとく
ちょ　ちょっと　監督～！
Hey! Manager!
はぁ～　王子が欠場とはなぁ
Geez, a match without Prince...
Well, even though the swelling of his leg isn't anything serious,
まあ　足の張りとはいっても
大したものじゃなさそうですが
it's probably true that he's worn out.
疲れがあるのは　事実でしょう
それを言ったら　ほかの連中だって同じだよ
It's the same case for everyone.
シーズンも半ばにさしかかって
We're halfway into the season,
so there's bound to be fatigue.
結構　疲れがたまってる
けど　何だかんだで 昨シーズンより
Still, Prince is playing through the matches at a high tempo.
ハイペースで試合に出てますからね　王子
う～ん　確かにね
That's true.
Last year, he even got tired of a match and requested to be subbed out.
去年は試合に飽きて
自ら途中交代を願い出るなんて 事もあったからなぁ
Crazy things did happen, didn't they...
ありましたねぇ
とんでもねえ話だけど
今でも　とんでもないとこ　ありますけど
They are still happening now, though.
However, Prince is playing so well this season that nobody's complaining.
でも　その王子が　今シーズンは
周りを黙らせるほどのパフォーマンスをしてるんだ
よっぽど　相性が合ったんだろうよ 達海　猛のサッカーが
It must have suited him really well...
Tatsumi's playing style, that is.
Yeah.
しかし　その王子抜きで　川崎戦 どう戦うつもりなんですかね　達海監督は
Still, I wonder how Tatsumi plans on facing Kawasumi without Prince.
Hmm...
決めた…　あれでいこう
Yup, let's go with that.
Gotou!
後藤
Oh, what's up, Tatsumi?
おう　どうした？　達海
You know... I'm so hungry.
あのさあ　俺さあ　腹減っちゃって
And, uh?
Will you treat me to curry? An extra big serving while you're at it?
カレー　おごってくんない？　大盛りで
Curry?
カレー？
Hey, guys.
よう　お前ら！
あ　ウイ～ッス
Hi.
カレー　好き？
Do you like curry?
Curry?
は？　カレー？
うん　カレー
Yup, curry. Don't like it?
食いたくない？
Well, I guess I like it.
まあ　好きっちゃ好きですけど
But what are you talking about?
つうか　何の話スか？
Then, please go ahead and buy these.
じゃあ買ってきて
Here's the money and the list of ingredients.
これ　お金と材料書いたメモ
I had the cafeteria ladies write that, so it should be correct.
さっき　食堂のおばちゃんに　計算してもらったから
きっと正確
Uhh...
あ　あのう…
チキンカレーだよ
It's chicken curry.
やっぱりスポーツ選手は鶏肉のほうがいいでしょう
Chicken is better for athletes, right?
I thought about going for Victory-Cutlet-Curry so we can win against our opponents,
カツカレーで「敵に勝つ」ってのも　考えたけど
but that's too cheesy.
あれって　そもそもダジャレだし
Alright.
ほんじゃ
Don't get the amount wrong.
量とか間違えんなよ
行ってらっしゃ～い！
Get going now.
W-What about practice?
れ…　練習は？
Locker Room
The hell is this?
何だこれ
…おい　コラ！
What do you mean? It's a leaflet.
何って…　チラシですけど
そういう事　聞いてんじゃねえよ！
That's not what I meant!
Why do we have to hand these out in town instead of practicing?!
なんで俺らが　こんなもん街で配ってこなきゃ　ならねえんだよ！
練習もしねえでよ
Leaflet: ETU Curry Party! All the players are waiting for you at the clubhouse. It's free, so let's all come and enjoy the food!
聞いてねえぞ俺　こんなのよ
I didn't sign up for this.
Besides, what the hell is a curry party?!
大体　何なんだよ
カレーパーティーって！
え～　でも　大抵の人って　カレー好きじゃね？
I mean, don't most people like curry?
そういう話　してるか　俺は？
That's not the point!
Can't you be serious for a minute?!
まじめ聞けよ！
とにかく　あんたの気まぐれの　お遊びには　こりごりなんだよ！
Anyway, I am sick and tired of your random games!
やるなら勝手にやってろ！ったく！
Do it alone if you wanna play them!
I can't believe that a pro player is refusing to interact with the local fans.
プロ選手ともあろうものが　地元の人たちとの交流をおろそかにするとはねぇ
Those are two different matters altogether!
そ　それとこれとは　関係ねえだろ
Oh, I get it! People won't come if it's Kuro.
あ　そうか 　クロじゃ　人集まんねえか
スギ　ちょっとだけ　行ってきてくんねえ？
Sugie, can you do this instead?
１５分だけだぞ
Only 15 minutes, okay?!
Oh, really? I'll leave it up to you then.
あ　ホント？
あ　じゃ頼むわ
Let's go, Sugie, Tsubaki!
行くぞ　スギ！　椿！
Hey, don't you think you're going a bit too far with your games?
おいおいお遊びが　過ぎんじゃねえのか？
Ha! Don't think you don't have work to do, Murakoshi.
自分は仕事がないと　思うなよ　村越
Hey! We're going to make curry for 100 people,
コラ～！ １００人分　カレー作るんだから
空いてる人　手伝って！
so those who are free, help out!
Stop dwaddling! You're free, right?!
さあ　グズグズしない！
ちょっと達海さん！
Tatsumi!
広報通さないで何やってんのよ！
Why are you doing this without informing the PR department?!
Wow, you look good in that.
おっ　似合ってんじゃん　有里
He even enlisted the help of the formidable cafeteria ladies.
食堂のパワフルおばちゃんたち　味方につけて
Just what is he planning?!
何がしたいのよ　達海さん！
おいおい　全員巻き込むつもりかよ
Wait, are you planning to get all of us involved?
そうだよ 　全員でカレー作るんだ
Yup, everyone's gonna make curry together.
よいしょ　よいしょ 　おいしくな～れ
Hope you'll be tasty.
We're having a curry party at ETU's clubhouse!
今日　ＥＴＵクラブハウスで　カレーパーティーをやります！
It's free of charge!
お金は要りません
ETU's on a winning streak!
連勝だぜ　連勝！ＥＴＵ
カ…　カレー　食べませんか？
Would you like to eat curry?
ああ～っ！　椿だ！
It's Tsubaki!
椿がいる！
Tsubaki is here!
Hey!
椿！
Please sign for us!
本物だ！
What are you doing here?!
サインして！
何やってんの？
What's this? A curry party?
何これ？　…カレーパーティーだって！
今日じゃん！　何それ！
It's today!
For real?!
Yeah, I'm not sure myself,
よく分かんないけど　みんなでやってて
but everyone's involved.
選手　みんな　いんの？
Will all the players be there?
Uh, yeah.
わ～　行く行く！
We're going!
んまあ！　ハンサムね
Oh, he's so handsome!
Ciao.
チャオ
Hey, I was out for a while, and what's all the commotion about, Tatsumi?
ちょっと出かけてる　スキに　何の騒ぎだよ　達海
Gotou, we're just having a curry feast.
カレー　ごちそうになってるよ　後藤
選手たちに息抜きさせるにしろ
There must be other ways to let the players relax.
やり方があるだろ
What if something bad happens?
何か問題でも起きたら　どうするんだ
何も起きてないよ
Nothing will happen.
見ろよ　みんなで仲よく　カレー食べてら
Look, everyone is eating the curry peacefully.
The curry is really good!
カレー　おいしくなってますよ！
The players,
選手も
はい　順番　順番並んで
Get in line.
the management,
フロントの人間も
Akasaki, how was playing in the national team?
ねえ赤崎　代表チームで…
the local people,
地元の人たちも
the cafeteria ladies, and the junior coaches.
食堂のおばちゃんも
ジュニアのコーチも
They're all here, sharing this moment together.
みんな一緒になって　一つの事を共有してる
Good luck, young man.
頑張れよ　にいちゃん
ウ…　ウス
Thanks.
これがクラブだよ　後藤
This is what a club is, Gotou.
There are only 11 people playing on the field.
ピッチに立って　プレーするのは１１人
But you can't get through the long season with just that.
でも　それだけじゃ　リーグ戦の長丁場は戦えない
ベンチ　フロント　サポーター　クラブに携わる　たくさんの人
Those on the bench, the management, the fans...
There are many people connected to the club.
そのすべてが同じ方向を向いて
All of them have to be united and fight for the same cause.
同じ気持ちで戦うんだ
ETU will become much more stronger if that happens.
それができりゃ　ＥＴＵは　もっともっと強くなる
そうだったな
You're right.
Ｗｅ　ａｒｅ　ｅａｓｔｈａｍ！
Ｗｅ　ａｒｅ　ｅａｓｔｈａｍ！　Ｗｏｏｏｏ！
ｅａｓｔｈａｍ！
Make way!
道を開けろ～！
The king has returned!
王様のご帰還だ！
確かに俺たちはそこで見た
Certainly, we saw it there -
A dream-like reality where a weak team defeats a strong one.
弱いチームが強いチームをやっつける夢のような現実
We saw the miracle known as Giant Killing.
ジャイアントキリングという奇跡を
よっしゃ～！
Tatsumi...
達海
Can ETU do it?
なれるか？　ＥＴＵは
Yeah, these guys can do it.
ああ　こいつらは　なれるよ
They can become such a club.
そういうクラブにさ
そうか！
I see...
ほんじゃ　これ
So, please take care of these bills.
お支払い　よろしく
Wait, it's coming out of my pocket?!
えっ　これ　俺のポケットマネーなの
You said you'd treat me, didn't you?!
おごるって言ったじゃん
シーズンは　まだまだ　これからだ　張り切っていこうぜ！
The season is far from over!
Let's go take them on!
Yeah!
As ETU Go Marching On On On
「Ａｓ　ＥＴＵ　Ｇｏ　Ｍａｒｃｈｉｎｇ　Ｏｎ　Ｏｎ　Ｏｎ」
Glory East Tokyo United
「Ｇｌｏｒｙ　Ｅａｓｔ　Ｔｏｋｙｏ　Ｕｎｉｔｅｄ　Ｇｌｏｒｙ　Ｅａｓｔ　Ｔｏｋｙｏ　Ｕｎｉｔｅｄ」
「Ａｓ　ＥＴＵ　Ｇｏ　Ｍａｒｃｈｉｎｇ　Ｏｎ　Ｏｎ　Ｏｎ」
As ETU Go Marching On On On
「Ｇｌｏｒｙ　Ｅａｓｔ　Ｔｏｋｙｏ　Ｕｎｉｔｅｄ　Ｇｌｏｒｙ　Ｅａｓｔ　Ｔｏｋｙｏ　Ｕｎｉｔｅｄ」
Glory East Tokyo United
As ETU Go Marching On On On
「Ａｓ　ＥＴＵ　Ｇｏ　Ｍａｒｃｈｉｎｇ　Ｏｎ　Ｏｎ　Ｏｎ」
Glory East Tokyo United
「Ｇｌｏｒｙ　Ｅａｓｔ　Ｔｏｋｙｏ　Ｕｎｉｔｅｄ　Ｇｌｏｒｙ　Ｅａｓｔ　Ｔｏｋｙｏ　Ｕｎｉｔｅｄ」
Ａｓ　ＥＴＵ　Ｇｏ　Ｍａｒｃｈｉｎｇ　Ｏｎ　Ｏｎ　Ｏｎ
As ETU Go Marching On On On
ETU!  ETU!  ETU!  ETU!  ETU!
ＥＴＵ！　ＥＴＵ！　ＥＴＵ！
ETU!  ETU!  ETU!  ETU!  ETU!  ETU!
ETU!!
Thanks for your support!
-FFFpeeps